1cpublishing.eu 2013-04-12

# 1C Publishing games news screenshots videos downloads and online shop

* * *

Last Update: 1st September 2007

* * *

**Privacy Policy** \- the following statement explains 1C Publishing EU's policy regarding the personal information.

**Privacy Statement**

The 1C Publishing EU website does not store or capture personal information (apart from the case of Registration – read below), but merely logs the user's IP address (Internet Protocol: standard allowing data to be transmitted between two devices) which is automatically recognized by the web server. For more information see the explanation bellow in article "Cookies"

**Registration**

1C Publishing EU may collect information from you, only if you voluntarily provide it to us in case of registration.  
In order to receive latest news on our games, events and contests invitations, 1C Publishing EU will require information including: your name, surname, e-mail address, age, country and sex. We may use your personal information for our internal marketing studies to constantly improve our services and products.

**Cookies**

 **1.**|  When you enter 1C Publishing EU website your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie. Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used.  
---|---  
 **2.**|  The site uses cookies for collecting user information; it does not collect any information about you except that required for system administration of the website. These cookies are pieces of data created when you visit a site, and contain a unique, anonymous number. They are stored in the cookie directory of your hard drive, and do not expire at the end of your session.  
 **3.**|  Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalized services cannot then be provided to that user.  
 | NB: Even if you haven't set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse our site anonymously until such time as you register for 1C Publishing EU website services.
